U.S. Railroad Boards of Arbitration, Conciliation and Mediation Records 5463
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Railroad Boards of Arbitration, Conciliation and Mediation Records
1916-1967
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Railroad Boards of Arbitration, Conciliation and Mediation
5463
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection consists of several sub-series of transcripts, hearings, and exhibits relating to government mediation and arbitration in the railroad industry.
5623357
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Andrew Rossner, July 29, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Grievance arbitration -- United States; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Railroads -- United States; Labor unions -- Railroads -- United States; United States.; United States. Railroad Board of Arbitration, Conciliation and Mediation.
5623357
- Pres. Emerg. Bd. 1941 (Box 1)
  - Transportation Brotherhoods vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, et al. copy 1, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Transportation Brotherhoods vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, et al. copy 2, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Transportation Brotherhoods vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, et al. copy 3, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 2-3, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 4-21, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 23-25, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 27-29, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 31-36, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 37-38, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 39-40, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 41-42, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 43-44, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 45-49, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 50-53, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 54-56, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 58-60, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Employees' Exhibit No. 119, 124, 126-129, 131-132, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Employees' Exhibits, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Transportation Employees' Exhibits, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Pres. Emerg. Bd. 1941, 49, 52, 55 (Box 2)
  - Report to the President by the Emergency Board, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Report to the President by the Emergency Board No. 97, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Report to the President by the Emergency Board No. 98, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Conductors' Graduated Rates Case: Brief on Behalf of the Railroads, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Conductors' Graduated Rates Case: Transcript of the Final Arguments for the Carriers, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Summary Statement of the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 4-7, 1919-1941 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 35, 44, 55-57, 60, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 61, 64, 85, 95, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 106, 109, 114-115, 117, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 125-127, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 128-131, 136, 138-141, 1937-1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 143-146, 161, 1937-1941 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 162, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 163, 169-171, 173, 178-183, 185, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 187-191, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 192-194, 201-203, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Carriers' Exhibit No. 205-211, 213, 219, 221, 223, 225-229, 232-234, etc., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Pres. Emerg. Bd. 1955, 38 (Box 3)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Opening Statement for the Carriers (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Part I-VI of the Brief for the Carriers (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 1-3, 9-12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 13 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 14 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 15-17, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 19-24 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 25-28 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 29-30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 31-33 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 34-35 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - The 1955 Firemen's Wage and Rules Case: Carriers' Exhibit No. 36, 38-40 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The 1967 Shop Employees Wage, Rules and Fringe Benefits Case: Board's Exhibits and Employees' Exhibit No. 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The 1967 Shop Employees Wage, Rules and Fringe Benefits Case: Employees' Exhibit No. 4-10 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - The 1967 Shop Employees Wage, Rules and Fringe Benefits Case: Employees' Exhibit No. 11-13 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Before the President's National Emergency Board, 1916-1938 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Scope and Contents
    Box